Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
  - Subseries II.1: Issues, 1981-2005
    - Issue 76, 2001 Summer
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 113)
      - Issue 77, 2001 Fall (Box 118)
      - General (Box 60)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--Creatures of Habit: Stories by Jill McCorkle, 2001 (Box 60)
    - Issue 78, 2001-2002 Winter (Americas)
      - General (Box 55)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Correspondence with Authors (Box 9)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 60)
        - El Arma En El Hombre by Horacio Castellanos Moya (Inscribed by the author to Betsy Sussler), 2001 (Box 60)
        - Deep Design: Nine Little Art Histories by Libby Lumpkin, undated (Box 60)
        - Flying: Practical Training for Beginners by Luca Buvoli, undated (Box 60)
        - Sleepless Nights by Oliver Herring, undated (Box 60)
      - Portrait Photographs--Company Segundo, undated (Box 55)
      - Printed Material--Artist's Catalogs, 2000-2001
        - Funt, John (Box 55)
        - Henriques, Anna Ruth (Box 55)
        - James, Merlin (Box 55)
        - Martins, Sylvia (Box 55)
        - Murray, Elizabeth (Box 55)
        - Nauman, Bruce (Box 55)
        - Palacios, Ana Patricia (Box 55)
        - Stephan, Gary (Box 55)
        - Tomaselli, Fred (Box 55)
        - Wilson, Jane (Box 55)
      - Printed Material--Exhibition Catalogs, 1999-2003 (Box 55)
      - Printed Material--Journal--Latin American Literature and Arts, No. 65, 2002 Fall (Box 55)
    - Issue 79, 2002 Spring
      - General (Box 7)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 7)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 118)
    - Issue 80, 2002 Summer
      - General (Box 108)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 71)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 108)
      - Issue (Box 118)
      - Printed Material--Pamphlet--Un Studio, undated (Box 108)
    - Issue 81, 2002 Fall
      - General (Box 42)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 42)
        - "Where do We Live" by Christopher Shinn, undated (Box 42)
        - "What Didn't Happen" by Christopher Shinn, undated (Box 42)
        - "The Coming World" by Christopher Shinn, undated (Box 42)
        - "Other People" by Christopher Shinn, undated (Box 42)
      - Printed Material--Program--"Three Tales" by Steve Reich and Beryl Korot (Box 42)
    - Issue 82, 2002-2003 Winter (Americas)
      - General (Box 43, 49)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Audio/Visual Material--VHS Tape. Steve Reich and Beryl Korot, Three Excerpts from "Three Tales" (Box 49)
      - Issue (Box 119)
    - Issue 83, 2003 Spring
      - General (Box 34)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Issue (Box 119)
    - Issue 84, 2003 Summer
      - General (Box 11)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Portrait Photographs--Khoury-Ghata, Venus, undated (Box 11)
    - Issue 85, 2003 Fall
      - General (Box 66)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
      - Audio Files--Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 113)
      - Issue (Box 66)
      - Printed Material--Exhibition Catalogs--ICI (Independent Curators International): New Traveling Exhibitions of Contemporary Art, 2003 (Box 66)
    - Issue 86, 2003-2004 Winter (Americas)
      - General (Box 58)
      - Art--Photographs--Nechvatal, Joseph (Box 43)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 43)
        - Mini Disks (Box 43)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 43)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Layout (Box 58)
      - Printed Material--Artist's Catalogs--Nechvatal, Joseph (Box 43)
      - Printed Material--Pamphlets
        - "Evoking a Caribbean" by Annalee Davis, undated (Box 43)
        - "White Skin, Black Kin: Speaking the Unspeakable" by Joscelyn Gardner, An Intervention into the Barbados Museum Galleries, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Issue 87, 2004 Spring
      - General (Box 41)
      - Audio Files (Box 113)
        - Audio Cassettes (Box 113)
        - Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 113)
      - Issue (Box 19)
      - Portrait Photographs--Farah, Nuruddin, undated (Box 41)
      - Printed Material--Book jacket for Links by Nuruddin Farah (Box 41)
      - Printed Material--Artist's Catalogs--Schatz, Chan, 2002-2003 (Box 41)
    - Issue 88, 2004 Summer
      - General (Box 41)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes--General (Box 113)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassette--Leth, Jordon (Box 47)
      - Audio Files--Mini Disks (Box 113)
      - Digital Files--CD-R (Box 113)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Printed Material--Journal--Poets & Writers Magazine, 2004 May-June (Box 47)
    - Issue 89, 2004 Fall
      - General (Box 13)
      - Digital Files--CD-R. BOMB Ads (Box 13)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Printed Material--Journal--Canadian Art, 2004 Spring (Box 13)
      - Printed Material--Pamphlet--Tarnation, a film by Jonathan Caouette, undated (Box 13)
    - Issue 90, Winter 2004/2005
      - General (Box 77)
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Portrait Photographs--Unidentified Man, undated (Box 77)
      - Letters Notes 2004 Contributions (Box 126)
      - Americas 05 (Editorial) (Box 126)
      - Dancing Wisdom by Yvonne Daniel (Box 126)
      - Conscripts of Modernity: The Tragedy of Colonial Enlightenment by David Scott (Box 126)
    - Issue 91, Spring 2005
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Artists on Artists: Rackstraw Downes on Rudy Burckhardt (Box 126)
      - Artists on Artists: Christine Hill on Danica Phelps (Box 126)
      - “Whitfield Lovell” by Tom Otterness (Box 126)
      - Cecily Brown -- Cover (Box 126)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 126)
      - Interview: Julie Mehretu by Lawrence Chua (Box 126)
      - Interview: Bruce Mau by Kathryn Simon (Box 126)
      - Interview: Brad Cloepfil by Stuart Horodner (Box 126)
      - Interview: Constant by Linda Boersma (Box 126)
      - Interview: Robert Antoni by Lawrence Scott (Box 126)
      - Artists on Artists: Angus Cook on Adam McEwen (Box 126)
      - Interview: Kiyoshi Kurosawa by Jim O’Rourke (Box 126)
      - Interview: Roscoe Mitchell by Anthony Coleman (Box 126)
      - Interview: Pearl Abraham by Aryeh Lev Stollman (Box 126)
      - Artists on Artists: Carlos Brillembourg on Guillermo Kuitca (Box 126)
      - Trinie Dalton -- Spring 05 (Box 126)
      - “In Love Blood Shall Flow” by Steve Almond (Spring 05) (Box 126)
      - “Lake Hollywood” by Jacob Forman (Box 126)
      - Kimiko Hahn -- SP 05 (Box 126)
      - Mei Chin (Box 126)
      - Alexander Theroux (Box 126)
      - Joy Katz (Box 126)
      - Sidney Wade Spring or Summer (Box 126)
      - Hernán Bravovalera, trs. Michael Dietz (Box 126)
      - Draft of Issue (Box 126)
    - Issue 92, Summer 2005
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - John Newman (Box 127)
      - Artists on Artists: Don Shillingburg on Beth Campbell (Box 127)
      - Artists on Artists: Nancy Barton on Sue de Beer (Box 127)
      - Paul Ramírez-Jonas (Box 127)
      - A Ver -- Profiles and Positions (Box 127)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 127)
      - Interview: Luc Tuymans by Kerry James Marshall (Box 127)
      - Interview: Paul Chan by Nell McClister (Box 127)
      - Interview: Allan Sekula by Edward Dimendberg (Box 127)
      - Interview: Heather McHugh by Matthea Harvey (Box 127)
      - Interview: Susan Wheeler by Robert Polito (Box 127)
      - Interview: Tony Conrad by Jay Sanders (Box 127)
      - Interview: George Steel by William Wegman (Box 127)
      - Interview: Miranda July by Rachel Kushner (Box 127)
      - Interview: Carolyn Cantor by Betsy Sussler (Box 127)
      - “Slam Gram” by Mary Morris (Box 127)
      - “The Proposal” by Michael O’Keefe (Box 127)
      - Mark Swartz (Box 127)
      - “Nine Come” by Elana Greenfield (Box 127)
      - “She’s Not Here” by Peter Orner (Box 127)
      - Short Stories by Mark Magill (Box 127)
      - Heather McHugh (Box 127)
      - Patricia Spears Jones (Box 127)
      - First Proof Proofs (Box 127)
    - Issue 93, Fall 2005
      - Issue (Box 119)
      - Artists on Artists: Lucy Raven on Adam Helms (Box 127)
      - Artists on Artists: Barry Schwabsky on Stanley Whitney (Box 127)
      - Artists on Artists: Saul Ostrow on Jon Kessler (Box 127)
      - Artists on Artists: Jan Estep on Clarence Morgan (Box 127)
      - Editor’s Corner (Box 127)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 127)
      - Forrest Gander and Eliot Weinberger in Conversation (Box 127)
      - Interview: Lionel Shriver by Jenefer Shute (Box 127)
      - Lincoln Perry’s Charlottesville: An Essay by Ann Beattie (Box 127)
      - Interview: Jennifer Bartlett by Elizabeth Murray (Box 127)
      - Interview: Jennifer Bartlett by Elizabeth Murray (2) (Box 127)
      - Interview: Arturo Herrera by Josiah McElheny (Box 127)
      - Interview: Yinka Shonibare by Anthony Downey (Box 127)
      - Interview: Noah Baumbach by Jonathan Lethem (Box 127)
      - Issue 93, Fall 2005 (Box 128)
      - George Lewis (Box 128)
      - Interview: David Rabe by Evangeline Morphos (Box 128)
      - “From American Genius, A Comedy” by Lynne Tillman (Box 128)
      - Poems by Peter Gizzi (Box 128)
      - “One Marvelous Thing” by Rikki Ducornet (Box 128)
      - Poems by Laurie Blauner (Box 128)
      - Anouar Benmalek trs. by Suzanne Ruta (Fall) (Box 128)
      - Excerpts from Waves Empty on the Tongue by Elena Alexander (Box 128)
      - Poems by Brenda Shaughnessy (Box 128)
      - Poems by Tomaz Salamun (Box 128)
      - “Teachable Moment” by Pierre Hauser (Box 128)
    - Issue 94, Winter 05/06
      - Cover/Miscellaneous (Box 128)
      - Contributors’ Biographies (Box 128)
      - Dr. Lakra (Box 128)
      - Artists on Artists: John Phillip Santos on Rolando Briseño (Box 128)
      - Priscilla Monge by Tamara Diaz Bringas (trs. Ezra Fitz) (Box 128)
      - Artists on Artists: Frances Richard on Laureana Toledo (Box 128)
      - Interview: Plastilina Mosh (Alejandro Rosso) by Erasmo Guerra (Box 128)
      - Interview: Andy Palacio by Chris Cozier (Box 128)
      - Interview: Pedro Reyes by Tatiana Cuevas (Box 128)
      - Interview: Regina José Galindo by Francisco Goldman (Box 128)
      - Interview: Pablo Vargas Lugo by Rubén Gallo (Box 128)
      - Interview: José Castillo by Carlos Brillembourg (Box 128)
      - Interview: Julieta Campos by Danubio Torres Fierro (Box 128)
      - Interview: Daniel Sada by Jose Manuel Prieto (Box 128)
      - Interview: José Luis Rivas by Mónica de la Torre (Box 128)
      - Interview: Beto Gomez by Carlos Gutierrez (Box 128)
      - Short Stories by Bernardo Esquinca (Box 128)
      - “Meteors” by Alvaro Enrigue (trs. Tanya Huntington) (Box 128)
      - Poems by Julián Herbert (Box 128)
      - Excerpts from Porque Parece Mentira La Verdad Nunca Se Sabe by Daniel Sada (Box 128)
      - Fragment from “The Sands of Shipwreck” by Julieta Campos (Box 128)
      - “A Season in Paradise” by Jose Luis Rivas (Box 128)
      - Short stories by Guillermo Fadaneli (Box 128)
      - Short stories by Eloy Urroz (Box 128)
      - Americas ’06 -- Editor’s Notes (Box 128)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 128)
      - Changes Entered (Box 128)
      - In Design Changes (Box 128)
      - Changes to Enter (Box 128)
      - Fact-Check #94 (Box 128)
    - Issue 95, Spring 2006
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: James Casebere on Brian Wood (Box 129)
      - On the Cover: Louise Lawler by Jim Welling (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: Andrea Means on Corban Walker (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: Keith May erson on Randy Wray (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: David Salle on Kate Manheim (Box 129)
      - Interview: Paula Fox by Lynne Tillman (Box 129)
      - Interview: Bernard-Henri Lévy y Frederic Tuten (Box 129)
      - Interview: Tacita Dean by Jeffrey Eugenides (Box 129)
      - Interview: Harrell Fletcher by Allan McCollum (Box 129)
      - Interview: Dana Schutz by Mei Chin (Box 129)
      - Interview: Adam Rapp by Marsha Norman (Box 129)
      - Interview: Judd Ne’eman by Janet Burstein (Box 129)
      - Interview: Antony by Charles Atlas (Box 129)
      - Short Stories by Roberto Bolaño (Box 129)
      - Short Stories by Etgar Keret (Box 129)
      - Poems by Matthea Harvey (Box 129)
      - “The Good Darkey” by Ned Sublette (adapted from The Year Before the Flood: Music, Murder, and the Legacy of Slavery in New Orleans ) (Box 129)
      - New Orleans Stories (Box 129)
      - Poems by Delisa Mulkey (Box 129)
      - Poems by Juan Carlos Galeano (trs. James Kimbrell (Box 129)
      - Excerpt from Birds in Fall by Brad Kessler (Box 129)
      - First Proof: Willy Monaghan (Box 129)
      - FP Proofs (Box 129)
      - Bluelines (Box 129)
    - Issue 96, Summer 2006
      - B96 Editor’s Choice (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: John Miller on Nicolás Guagnini (Box 129)
      - Steven Charles by Dona Nelson (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: Mimi Thompson and Keith Sonnier on Luis Lleo (Box 129)
      - Artists on Artists: Tony Fitzpatrick (Box 129)
      - Photographs by Jason Langer (Box 129)
      - Interview: Jesper Just by Rose Lee Goldberg (Box 129)
      - Interview: Jane Dickson by Liz Larner (Box 129)
      - Interview: Bernard Piffaretti by Joe Fyfe (Box 129)
      - Interview: Tony Oursler by Alan Licht (Box 129)
      - Interview: Anthony Coleman by Michael Goldberg (Box 129)
      - Issue 96, Summer 2006 (Box 130)
      - Colm Tóibín and Chris Abani in Conversation (Box 130)
      - Interview: Kimiko Hahn by Laurie Sheck (Box 130)
      - Interview: Mei Mei Berssenbrugge by Michèle Gerber Klein (Box 130)
      - Interview: William Forsythe b Gabriella de Ferrari (Box 130)
      - Interview: Park Chanwook by Esther Chae (Box 130)
      - Interview: AR Gurne by Romulus Linney (Box 130)
      - Excerpt from Feelings are Facts (MIT Press), “First Proof” by Yvonne Rainer (Box 130)
      - “A Measure of Respect” by Kelvin Christopher James (Box 130)
      - Poems by Dana Caspersen (Box 130)
      - Poems by Dennis Cooper (Box 130)
      - “Gifts from New Orleans” by Guy Gallo (Box 130)
      - “The Strange Case of Rachel K” by Rachel Kushner (Box 130)
    - Issue 97, Fall 2006
      - BOMB 97 Front Matter (Box 130)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 130)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 130)
      - Interview: Theresa Rebeck by Evangeline Morphos (Box 130)
      - Interview: Judith Linhares by Madison Smartt Bell (Box 130)
      - Interview: William Katavalos by Deborah Gans (Box 130)
      - Nichole Argo and Omar Amanat (Box 131)
      - Interview: Lynne Tillman by Geoffrey O’Brien (Box 131)
      - Interview: Steven Shainberg by Andy Fierberg (Box 131)
      - Interview: Anthony McCall by Graham Ellard and Stephen Johnstone (Box 131)
      - Interview: Tod Papageorge by Rick Woodward (Box 131)
      - Interview: Amina Claudine Myers by George Lewis (Box 131)
      - “Nabokov’s Matches” by Sasha Chavchavadze (Box 131)
      - First Proof (Box 131)
    - Issue 98, Winter 2007
      - Front Matter and Layout (Box 131)
      - Proofreading (finished) (Box 131)
      - Artists on Artists: Bill FitzGibbons on Alex Rubio (Box 131)
      - Artists on Artists: Roberto Juarez on Paul Henry Ramirez (Box 131)
      - Artists on Artists: Trinie Dalton on Minerva Cuevas (Box 131)
      - Interview: Gronk by Marisela Norte (Box 131)
      - Interview: Salvador Plascencia by Max Benavidez
      - Issue 98, Winter 2007 (Box 132)
      - Interview: Virginia Fields by Constance Cortez (Box 132)
      - “Margo in the City of Equivocation” by Álvaro Enrigue (Box 132)
      - Interview: Doña Julia Casimiro by Jesuita Natalia Pineda Casimiro (Box 132)
      - Interview: Jorge Hernandez by Josh Kun (Box 132)
      - Interview: Cherríe Moraga by Adelina Anthony (Box 132)
      - Interview: Gabriel Orozco by Carmen Boullosa (Box 132)
      - Interview: Alberto Kalach by Jose Castillo (Box 132)
      - First Proof #98 (Box 132)
      - Performa 05 (Box 132)
      - Plate Betsy’s (Box 132)
      - Toc Fetch and Tricia Cline (Box 132)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 132)
    - Issue 99, Spring 2007
      - “The Great Lawn” by Iris Smyles (Box 132)
      - An Excerpt from I’Jaam: An Iraqi Rhapsody by Sinan Antoon (Box 132)
      - “Belisario” by Virgilio Piñera (trs. Mark Schafer) (Box 132)
      - Short Stories by Ben Ehrenreich (Box 132)
      - Excerpts from Like Son by Felicia Luna Lemus (Box 132)
      - Poems by Patricia Carlin (Box 132)
      - First Proof Issue 99 (Box 132)
      - Finals on Ads and Mail Contacts (Box 132)
      - Short Stories by Ali Bujnowski (Box 132)
      - Poems by Amanda Aucther (Box 132)
      - “The Portrait” by Mary Morris (Box 132)
      - Photographs by Gerald Slota (Box 132)
      - Interview: Lore Segal by Han Ong (Box 132)
      - Interview: John Turturro by June Stein (Box 132)
      - Interview: Robert Polidori by Michele Gerber Klein (Box 132)
      - Interview: Sarah Ruhl by Paula Vogel (Box 132)
      - Interview: Reinhold Friedl by Elliott Sharp (Box 132)
      - Issue 99, Spring 2007 (Box 133)
      - Interview: Mary Jordan by Nayland Blake (Box 133)
      - Interview: Cristina García by Chris Abani (Box 133)
      - Interview: Bill Jensen by John Yau (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Steve Kurtz on Doug Ashford (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Steve Kurtz on Doug Ashford (2) (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Marjorie Welish on Joe Fyfe (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Ryan Nole on Rose Garcia (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Bob Holman on Jessica Craig-Martin (Box 133)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Amy Sillman on Ellen Berkenblit (Box 133)
      - Front Matter and Layouts (Box 133)
      - Various TOC, Contributors, Ads, Pages from Issue 99 (Box 133)
      - F.C. Issue 99 (Box 133)
    - Issue 100, Summer 2007
      - Front Matter (Box 133)
      - Contributors and TOC Issue 100 (Box 133)
      - BOMB Celebrates its 25th Year (Box 133)
      - On the Cover: Jennifer Clifford Danner by Betsy Sussler (Box 133)
      - Editor’s Choice (Bas Jan Ader) (Box 133)
      - Editor’s Choice (Books) (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Rochelle Feinstein on Pam Lins (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Steve Earle on Robbie Conal (Box 133)
      - Artists on Artists: Trevor Paglen on Nicola López (Box 133)
      - Interview: Karin Mamma by Christian Hawkey (Box 133)
      - Interview: Béla Tarr by Fionn Meade (Box 133)
      - Interview: Peter Nádas by Davis Kovacs (Box 133)
      - Interview: Joe Zucker by Chuck Close (Box 133)
      - Interview: Benedict Mason by George Steel (Box 133)
      - Interview: Kate Valk by Kendall Grady (Box 133)
      - Interview: Kara Walker by Matthea Harvey (Box 133)
      - Interview: Howard Norman by Susan Shreve (Box 133)
      - Excerpts from The Dizzies by Ed Park (Box 133)
      - “In My Yoke Skirt” by Diane Williams (Box 133)
      - Poems by Anne Carson (Box 133)
      - “What Happened Between Us” by Riuka Galchen (Box 133)
      - Excerpts from Incantations: Songs, Spells, and Images by May an Women edited by Ambar Past (Box 133)
      - The Life Room by Jill Bialosky (Box 133)
      - Issue 100 Fact Check (Box 133)
      - Calendar/Planner for 2006 and Miscellaneous Papers (Box 133)
      - Note of Congratulations from Alexis and the College Art Association Staff (Box 133)
    - Issue 101, Fall 2007
      - Aric’s Photo’s for BOMB 101 (Box 134)
      - Issue 101, Fall 2007 (Box 134)
      - Front Matter and Layouts (Box 134)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 134)
      - Artists on Artists (Box 134)
      - Artists on Artists: Joe Fyfe on Andrzej Zielinski (Box 134)
      - Interview: David Malouf by Colm Toibin (Box 134)
      - Interview: Peter Doig by Chris Ofili (Box 134)
      - “Big Dance Theater” by John Haskell (Box 134)
      - Interview: R. Stevie Moore by David Shrigley (Box 134)
      - Interview: Richard Pare by Michèle Gerber Klein (Box 134)
      - Interview: Winter Miller by Evangeline Morphos (Box 134)
      - Manon de Boer and Marine Hugonnier in Conversation (Box 134)
      - Interview: Junot Diaz by Edwidge Danticat (Box 134)
      - The Zero Meter Driving Team by Jim Shepard (A Collection of Short Stories) (Box 134)
      - Interview: Idris Khan by Adam Fuss (Box 134)
      - First Proof: “Fish” by Anu Lakhan (Box 134)
      - First Proof: Harold Schechter (Box 134)
      - “Roof Topped” by Terese Svoboda (Box 134)
      - Administrative Files: Minutes and Potential Board (Box 134)
      - Administrative Files: Sawn 12/12/06 (Box 134)
      - Administrative Files: Consortium (Box 134)
      - Administrative Files: Award (Box 134)
      - Administrative Files: IPA (Box 134)
      - Interview: Isaac Julien by Martina Kudlacek (Box 134)
      - 2006/2007 Message Book of Betsy Sussler (Box 134)
      - Correspondence Related to the Doig/Ofili Interview (Box 134)
    - Issue 102, Winter 2008
      - Front Matter (Box 135)
      - Artists on Artists: Laura Lima by Cabelo (Box 135)
      - Artists on Artists: Mario Ramiro on Lucia Koch (Box 135)
      - Artists on Artists: Luis Andrade on Jarbas Lopes (Box 135)
      - Interview: Bernardo Carvalho by Natalia Brizuela (Box 135)
      - Artists on Artists: Botika on Thiago Rocha Pitta (Box 135)
      - Interview: the Campana Bothers (Humberto and Fernando) by Vik Muniz (Box 135)
      - Interview: Cao Guimarães and Marilá Dardot (trs. Odile Cisneros) (Box 135)
      - Interview: Karim Ainoz by Tania Cypriano (Box 135)
      - Os Gémeos and the Campana Brothers (Box 135)
      - Interview: Arnaldo Antunes by Euncanaã Ferraz (trs. Claudio Brandt) (Box 135)
      - Interview: Paulo Mendes da Rocha by Ruth Verde Zein (Box 135)
      - Interview: Francisco Alvim by Antonio Sergio Bessa (Box 135)
      - Interview: Fernanda Gomes by Ernesto Neto (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- Barrão (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- “Alice and the Old Lady” by Cristovão Tezza (trs. Johnny Lorenz) (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- “Fortunate Buddhas” by João Ubaldo Ribeiro (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- Poems by Adélia Prado (trs. Ellen Doré Watson) (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- An Excerpt from Jonas by Patrícia Melo (trs. Clifford E. Landers) (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- Poems by Salgado Maranhão (trs. Alexis Levitin) (Box 135)
      - “Olivia and Xania” by Rubem Fonseca (trs. Clifford E. Landers) (Box 135)
      - FP -- Correspondence Related to Nelida Piñon (Box 135)
      - Lygia Fagundes and Manuel Alegre in Conversation (Box 135)
      - Artists on Artists: Tunga on Otávio Schipper (Box 135)
      - Pile of First Proof Stuff (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- Decio Pignatari (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- “Hunger and the Will to Eat” by Cintia Moscovich (trs. Idra Novey) (Box 135)
      - First Proof -- Poems by Manoel de Barros (Box 135)
      - BRAZIL! (Box 135)
    - Issue 103, Spring 2008 and Summary
      - Front Matter (Box 136)
      - Editor’s Choice (Box 136)
      - Artists on Artists: James Siena on Chris Martin (Box 136)
      - Artists on Artists: Elka Krajewska on Pôline de Pôlogne (Box 136)
      - Artists on Artists: Betsy Sussler on Rachel Foullon (Box 136)
      - Klava Hobza (Box 136)
      - Interview: Harmony Korine by Richard Bishop (Box 136)
      - Lydia Millet and Jonathan Lethem in Conversation (Box 136)